{"head": "Apple", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "Cupertino", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9618849158287048, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/business/company/place_founded", 0.9618849158287048], ["/sports/sports_team/location", 0.006252983119338751], ["/people/deceased_person/place_of_death", 0.004503515549004078], ["/business/company/major_shareholders", 0.0038732639513909817], ["/business/company/advisors", 0.0031910776160657406]], "note": null}
{"head": "Apple", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Tim Cook", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9825550317764282, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": [["/business/company/founders", 0.9825550317764282], ["/business/company/major_shareholders", 0.007197903003543615], ["/people/person/children", 0.0012405063025653362], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.001222530729137361], ["/business/person/company", 0.000987741514109075]], "note": null}
{"head": "Apple", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "California", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9638102054595947, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/business/company/place_founded", 0.9638102054595947], ["/sports/sports_team/location", 0.006838316097855568], ["/business/company/major_shareholders", 0.0041946591809391975], ["/business/company/advisors", 0.003582807956263423], ["/people/deceased_person/place_of_death", 0.0029356474988162518]], "note": null}
{"head": "Cupertino", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "California", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9978958368301392, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9978958368301392], ["/location/country/capital", 0.00047144611016847193], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.0003340386028867215], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.0003158219624310732], ["/people/person/place_lived", 0.00018556849681772292]], "note": null}
{"head": "Tim Cook", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Apple", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9966159462928772, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": [["/business/person/company", 0.9966159462928772], ["/business/company_shareholder/major_shareholder_of", 0.001030630199238658], ["/people/person/place_lived", 0.0006722261314280331], ["/people/person/place_of_birth", 0.0003525594947859645], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.0002712740679271519]], "note": null}
{"head": "Tim Cook", "relation": "/people/person/place_lived", "tail": "Cupertino", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.874719500541687, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/people/person/place_lived", 0.874719500541687], ["/people/person/place_of_birth", 0.10431255400180817], ["/people/deceased_person/place_of_death", 0.018305789679288864], ["/business/person/company", 0.0010597908403724432], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.00035984188434667885]], "note": null}
{"head": "Tim Cook", "relation": "/people/person/place_lived", "tail": "California", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.541822612285614, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/people/person/place_lived", 0.541822612285614], ["/people/person/place_of_birth", 0.24434147775173187], ["/business/person/company", 0.1945725381374359], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.0082591213285923], ["/people/deceased_person/place_of_death", 0.006675765383988619]], "note": null}
{"head": "California", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Cupertino", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9993696808815002, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9993696808815002], ["/location/country/capital", 0.00024846650194376707], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.0001795505959307775], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 3.7033776607131585e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 3.4920081816380844e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Google", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "Mountain View", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9640883803367615, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/business/company/place_founded", 0.9640883803367615], ["/sports/sports_team/location", 0.007263965904712677], ["/business/company/major_shareholders", 0.004182302858680487], ["/business/company/advisors", 0.003626675345003605], ["/people/deceased_person/place_of_death", 0.0032077378127723932]], "note": null}
{"head": "Google", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Larry Page", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.8245223760604858, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": [["/business/company/founders", 0.8245223760604858], ["/business/company/major_shareholders", 0.15420575439929962], ["/business/company/advisors", 0.003301089396700263], ["/business/company_shareholder/major_shareholder_of", 0.0028431888204067945], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.0025158359203487635]], "note": null}
{"head": "Google", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Sergey Brin", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.687736451625824, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": [["/business/company/founders", 0.687736451625824], ["/business/company/major_shareholders", 0.2838287949562073], ["/business/company/advisors", 0.004755957517772913], ["/business/company_shareholder/major_shareholder_of", 0.0039060749113559723], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.0038419263437390327]], "note": null}
{"head": "Larry Page", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Google", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.8190357089042664, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": [["/business/person/company", 0.8190357089042664], ["/business/company_shareholder/major_shareholder_of", 0.1691865772008896], ["/business/company/founders", 0.002098332392051816], ["/people/person/children", 0.0015429217601194978], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.0008853796753101051]], "note": null}
{"head": "Sergey Brin", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Google", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.7501163482666016, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": [["/business/person/company", 0.7501163482666016], ["/business/company_shareholder/major_shareholder_of", 0.23423928022384644], ["/business/company/founders", 0.0030723882373422384], ["/people/person/children", 0.0018444783054292202], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.0012521930038928986]], "note": null}
{"head": "Russia", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Astana", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.6672032475471497, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.6672032475471497], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.30704084038734436], ["/location/country/capital", 0.025032641366124153], ["/location/administrative_division/country", 9.338264499092475e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 8.501337288180366e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Moscow", "relation": "/location/administrative_division/country", "tail": "Russia", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9991474151611328, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/administrative_division/country", 0.9991474151611328], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.0001404414069838822], ["/people/ethnicity/geographic_distribution", 8.316641469718888e-05], ["/business/company/industry", 7.60755137889646e-05], ["/people/person/profession", 6.02540785621386e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Moscow", "relation": "/location/administrative_division/country", "tail": "Kazakhstan", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.999143123626709, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/administrative_division/country", 0.999143123626709], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.0001207260211231187], ["/people/ethnicity/geographic_distribution", 8.298105967696756e-05], ["/business/company/industry", 7.595941860927269e-05], ["/people/person/profession", 6.034243415342644e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Kazakhstan", "relation": "/location/administrative_division/country", "tail": "Russia", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9989619255065918, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/administrative_division/country", 0.9989619255065918], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.00020058454538229853], ["/people/ethnicity/geographic_distribution", 0.00013818724255543202], ["/business/company/industry", 9.560574108036235e-05], ["/people/person/profession", 7.730635843472555e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Astana", "relation": "/location/administrative_division/country", "tail": "Russia", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.998302698135376, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/administrative_division/country", 0.998302698135376], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.0005947746685706079], ["/people/ethnicity/geographic_distribution", 0.0001648444012971595], ["/business/company/industry", 0.00012201901699882001], ["/people/person/profession", 9.810601477511227e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Astana", "relation": "/location/administrative_division/country", "tail": "Moscow", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.5194084644317627, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/administrative_division/country", 0.5194084644317627], ["/location/country/capital", 0.1768409162759781], ["/location/location/contains", 0.14116141200065613], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.041157517582178116], ["/people/deceased_person/place_of_death", 0.030678139999508858]], "note": null}
{"head": "Astana", "relation": "/location/administrative_division/country", "tail": "Kazakhstan", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9990536570549011, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/administrative_division/country", 0.9990536570549011], ["/people/person/nationality", 0.00018908182391896844], ["/people/ethnicity/geographic_distribution", 9.515386773273349e-05], ["/business/company/industry", 8.072916534729302e-05], ["/people/person/profession", 6.483134347945452e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "New York", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9993700385093689, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9993700385093689], ["/location/country/capital", 0.0002455315843690187], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.00018694937170948833], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 3.997454768978059e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 3.639387432485819e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "New York", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9993703961372375, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9993703961372375], ["/location/country/capital", 0.0002383270038990304], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.0001688258198555559], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 4.4358250306686386e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 4.0238133806269616e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "New York", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Long Island City", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9993731379508972, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9993731379508972], ["/location/country/capital", 0.0002528969489503652], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.00017888344882521778], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 3.72866888938006e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 3.406648102100007e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Manhattan", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "New York", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9896411299705505, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9896411299705505], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.006896669045090675], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.0009621692006476223], ["/location/country/capital", 0.0005295050796121359], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.0005091846105642617]], "note": null}
{"head": "Manhattan", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.99931800365448, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.99931800365448], ["/location/country/capital", 0.0002167413040297106], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.0001457708713132888], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 7.301076402654871e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 6.148422107798979e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Manhattan", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Long Island City", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9993618130683899, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9993618130683899], ["/location/country/capital", 0.00023482124379370362], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.00015677817282266915], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 5.120505011291243e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 4.656105738831684e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "the Upper West Side", "relation": "/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", "tail": "New York", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9990922212600708, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "FAC", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.9990922212600708], ["/location/location/contains", 0.00012272446474526078], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.00011681851174216717], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 8.194069960154593e-05], ["/business/company/industry", 6.80320372339338e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "the Upper West Side", "relation": "/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9991256594657898, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "FAC", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.9991256594657898], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.00011206441558897495], ["/location/location/contains", 0.0001029722043313086], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 7.57227317080833e-05], ["/business/company/industry", 6.886813207529485e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "the Upper West Side", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Long Island City", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9943220615386963, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "FAC", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9943220615386963], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.0038605595473200083], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.00041660197894088924], ["/location/country/capital", 0.00038775362190790474], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.0002586111659184098]], "note": null}
{"head": "Queens", "relation": "/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", "tail": "New York", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9956367611885071, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.9956367611885071], ["/location/location/contains", 0.002644716529175639], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.0003436201368458569], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.0003415362152736634], ["/sports/sports_team/location", 0.00011914267088286579]], "note": null}
{"head": "Queens", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9853289723396301, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9853289723396301], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.012318890541791916], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.0005791480070911348], ["/location/country/capital", 0.00039752552402205765], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.000331251067109406]], "note": null}
{"head": "Queens", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9993182420730591, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9993182420730591], ["/location/country/capital", 0.00022332565276883543], ["/location/country/administrative_divisions", 0.00014621407899539918], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 7.44497956475243e-05], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 6.0298181779216975e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Long Island City", "relation": "/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", "tail": "New York", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9990975856781006, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.9990975856781006], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.00013403053162619472], ["/location/location/contains", 0.00011060529504902661], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 8.443949627690017e-05], ["/business/company/industry", 6.594027945538983e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Long Island City", "relation": "/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.999114453792572, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": [["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.999114453792572], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.00012748301378451288], ["/location/location/contains", 0.0001071710285032168], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 7.99158078734763e-05], ["/business/company/industry", 6.66139749228023e-05]], "note": null}
{"head": "Long Island City", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9395331740379333, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": [["/location/location/contains", 0.9395331740379333], ["/location/neighborhood/neighborhood_of", 0.05263173580169678], ["/sports/sports_team_location/teams", 0.002384827472269535], ["/business/company/place_founded", 0.001701591070741415], ["/location/country/capital", 0.000855534162838012]], "note": null}
{"head": "Elon Musk", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Tesla", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.9941985607147217, "sent_id": 4, "sentence": "Elon Musk is associated with Tesla, and Tesla has major shareholders including Elon Musk.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": [["/business/person/company", 0.9941985607147217], ["/business/company_shareholder/major_shareholder_of", 0.0040427702479064465], ["/people/person/place_lived", 0.000495930842589587], ["/people/person/children", 0.00020990835037082434], ["/business/company/founders", 0.00020057940855622292]], "note": null}
{"head": "Tesla", "relation": "/business/company/major_shareholders", "tail": "Elon Musk", "source": "spanbert", "conf": 0.7159279584884644, "sent_id": 4, "sentence": "Elon Musk is associated with Tesla, and Tesla has major shareholders including Elon Musk.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": [["/business/company/major_shareholders", 0.7159279584884644], ["/business/company/founders", 0.24229012429714203], ["/business/company/advisors", 0.008375482633709908], ["/business/company_shareholder/major_shareholder_of", 0.006393409799784422], ["/people/person/children", 0.004035193007439375]], "note": null}
{"head": "Apple", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "Cupertino", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Apple was founded in Cupertino."}
{"head": "Apple", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Tim Cook", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": null, "note": "Tim Cook is mentioned as leading Apple, indicating he has a company relationship with Apple."}
{"head": "Apple", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "California", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Apple was founded in Cupertino and Tim Cook led Apple from California, implying the company is associated with the location California."}
{"head": "Cupertino", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "California", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Apple was founded in Cupertino and mentions California, which could imply the state where Cupertino is located."}
{"head": "Tim Cook", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Apple", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Tim Cook later led Apple, indicating an employment relationship between the person and the company."}
{"head": "Tim Cook", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Cupertino", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "Tim Cook is mentioned as leading Apple, implying he was associated with the company."}
{"head": "Tim Cook", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "California", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "Tim Cook is mentioned as leading Apple, implying he was associated with the company."}
{"head": "California", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "Cupertino", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 0, "sentence": "Apple was founded in Cupertino, and Tim Cook later led Apple from California.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Apple was founded in Cupertino, which implies the place of founding."}
{"head": "Google", "relation": "/business/company/place_founded", "tail": "Mountain View", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Google was founded in Mountain View, which directly indicates the place of founding."}
{"head": "Google", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Larry Page", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Google was founded by Larry Page and Sergey Brin, indicating a founders relationship."}
{"head": "Google", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Sergey Brin", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Google was founded by Larry Page and Sergey Brin, indicating a founder relationship."}
{"head": "Larry Page", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Google", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Google was founded by Larry Page and Sergey Brin, which implies a founder relationship."}
{"head": "Larry Page", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Mountain View", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Google was founded by Larry Page and Sergey Brin, implying Larry Page is a founder of the company. However, Mountain View is not directly related to Larry Page as a founder in this context."}
{"head": "Sergey Brin", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Google", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Google was founded by Sergey Brin and Larry Page."}
{"head": "Sergey Brin", "relation": "/business/company/founders", "tail": "Mountain View", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 1, "sentence": "Google was founded in Mountain View by Larry Page and Sergey Brin.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Google was founded by Larry Page and Sergey Brin, which implies Sergey Brin is a founder of the company. Mountain View is mentioned as the place of founding, not directly related to Sergey Brin's role."}
{"head": "Russia", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Moscow", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Moscow is the capital of Russia."}
{"head": "Russia", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Kazakhstan", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence mentions the capitals of Russia and Kazakhstan, but does not directly state a relation between the two countries."}
{"head": "Russia", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Astana", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Moscow is the capital of Russia and Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan, which implies a capital-city relationship."}
{"head": "Moscow", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Russia", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Moscow is the capital of Russia."}
{"head": "Moscow", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Kazakhstan", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Moscow is the capital of Russia and Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan, implying a capital-country relationship."}
{"head": "Moscow", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Astana", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Moscow is the capital of Russia and Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan, establishing a capital-city relationship between each entity and its respective country."}
{"head": "Kazakhstan", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Russia", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence mentions that Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan, which implies a relation between the two countries regarding their capitals."}
{"head": "Kazakhstan", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Moscow", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan, which implies that Moscow is not related to Kazakhstan as a capital city."}
{"head": "Kazakhstan", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Astana", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan."}
{"head": "Astana", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Russia", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan, and Russia is mentioned as a different country, establishing a relation between a country and its capital."}
{"head": "Astana", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Moscow", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan, while Moscow is the capital of Russia, indicating a capital-city relationship."}
{"head": "Astana", "relation": "/location/country/capital", "tail": "Kazakhstan", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 2, "sentence": "In Russia, Moscow is the capital, but in Kazakhstan, Astana is the capital.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Astana is the capital of Kazakhstan."}
{"head": "New York", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, which implies a containment relationship between New York and Manhattan."}
{"head": "New York", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side."}
{"head": "New York", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Long Island City", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side and Queens contains Long Island City, indicating a containment relationship."}
{"head": "Manhattan", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "New York", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and by extension, it implies that New York contains Manhattan."}
{"head": "Manhattan", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side."}
{"head": "Manhattan", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Long Island City", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side and Queens contains Long Island City, indicating a containment relationship."}
{"head": "the Upper West Side", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "New York", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "FAC", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side and Queens contains Long Island City, implying a containment relationship between New York and the Upper West Side."}
{"head": "the Upper West Side", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "FAC", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side."}
{"head": "the Upper West Side", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Long Island City", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "FAC", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Manhattan contains the Upper West Side and Queens contains Long Island City, which implies a containment relationship."}
{"head": "Queens", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "New York", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Queens contains Long Island City, which implies a location containment relation."}
{"head": "Queens", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Queens contains Long Island City and Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, indicating a containment relationship."}
{"head": "Queens", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Queens contains Long Island City and Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, indicating a containment relationship."}
{"head": "Queens", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Long Island City", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Queens contains Long Island City."}
{"head": "Long Island City", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "New York", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Queens contains Long Island City, and Manhattan contains the Upper West Side. Although New York is mentioned as a GPE, there's no explicit relation stated between Long Island City and New York in the given sentence."}
{"head": "Long Island City", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "Manhattan", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "GPE", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Queens contains Long Island City and Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, indicating a containment relationship."}
{"head": "Long Island City", "relation": "/location/location/contains", "tail": "the Upper West Side", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 3, "sentence": "In New York, Manhattan contains the Upper West Side, and Queens contains Long Island City.", "head_type": "GPE", "tail_type": "FAC", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Queens contains Long Island City, which implies a containment relation between the two locations."}
{"head": "Elon Musk", "relation": "/business/person/company", "tail": "Tesla", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 4, "sentence": "Elon Musk is associated with Tesla, and Tesla has major shareholders including Elon Musk.", "head_type": "PERSON", "tail_type": "ORG", "topk": null, "note": "Elon Musk is associated with Tesla, indicating he has a company relation with it."}
{"head": "Tesla", "relation": "/business/company/major_shareholders", "tail": "Elon Musk", "source": "llm", "conf": 1.0, "sent_id": 4, "sentence": "Elon Musk is associated with Tesla, and Tesla has major shareholders including Elon Musk.", "head_type": "ORG", "tail_type": "PERSON", "topk": null, "note": "The sentence states that Tesla has major shareholders including Elon Musk, which implies Elon Musk is one of the major shareholders of Tesla."}
